var trivia = [{
    question: "Whao believes that despair is the stepping stone for hope?",
    choices: ["Hajime", "Kyoko", "Sakura", "Nagito"],
    correctAnswer: 3
}, {
    question: "Byakuya is the heir to which major company?",
    choices: ["Togami Industries", "Togami Corporation", " Super Togami", "BT inc."],
    correctAnswer: 1
}, {
    question: "What real game was played during chapter 2 of Danganronpa 2?",
    choices: ["Super Mario Bros", "Twilight Syndrome Murder Case", "Ultra Despair Girls", "Final Fantasy 7"],
    correctAnswer: 1
}, {
    question: "Who becomes the successor to Junko is Danganronpa Another Episode?",
    choices: ["Monica", "Nagisa", "Kurokuma", "Kotoko"],
    correctAnswer: 0
}, {
    question: "What is the name of the computer program Chihiro created during the killing game?",
    choices: ["AI", "Chi Chat", " Alter Ego", "Kuma"],
    correctAnswer: 2
}, {
    question: "Who was inflicted with gullible despair disease during chapter 3 of Danganronpa 2?",
    choices: ["Nagito", "Hiyoko", "Mikan", "Ibuki"],
    correctAnswer: 3
}, {
    question: "What title was Makoto granted at the end of Danganronpa 1?",
    choices: ["Ultimate Protagonist", "Ultimate Average Guy", "Ultimate Despair", "Ultimate Hope"],
    correctAnswer: 3
}, {
    question: "Who do the Warriors of Hope loathe?",
    choices: ["Kids", "Adults", " Hope", "Despair"],
    correctAnswer: 1
}, {
    question: "What real game was played during chapter 2 of Danganronpa 2?",
    choices: ["Super Mario Bros", "Twilight Syndrome Murder Case", "Ultra Despair Girls", "Final Fantasy 7"],
    correctAnswer: 2
}, {
    question: "Who does Kiyotaka form an unlikely bromance with?",
    choices: ["Mondo", "Hifumi", "Yasuhiro", "Makoto"],
    correctAnswer: 0
}];